dwuser.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Legal - DWUser.com

_(Effective December 12, 2012)_

Welcome to DWUser.com ("Website"), an interactive online service operated by Magnetic Marketing & Services, Inc. ("Magnetic Marketing Corp.", "us", "we", or "our").  Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy.

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website.  We have adopted this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on the Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties.  This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.

This Privacy Policy sets forth the general rules and policies governing your use of the Website.  Depending on your activities when visiting the Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

We generally keep this Privacy Policy posted on the Website and you should review it frequently, as it may change from time to time.  Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy.  WHEN YOU ACCESS THE WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.  IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, OR TO ANY CHANGES WE MAY SUBSEQUENTLY MAKE, IMMEDIATELY STOP ACCESSING THE WEBSITE. 

###  Information We Collect and How We Use It

Please read this Privacy Policy in full.  If, after reading the policy in its entirety, you wish to later access certain sections more easily, the following links may be used.  THE FOLLOWING LINKS ARE PROVIDED ONLY AS A NAVIGATION TOOL AND DO NOT REPRESENT THE EXTENT OR SCOPE OF THIS POLICY.  YOU AGREE TO ONLY USE THESE LINKS AFTER READING THE POLICY IN FULL.

  * Email list information, including opt-out information
  * Sharing and disclosure of your information
  * How to contact us

The Website typically collects two kinds of information about you: (a) information that you provide that personally identifies you; and (b) information that does not personally identify you, but that we automatically collect when you visit the Website or that you provide us.

####  Information you give us

**Financial information** : When you purchase goods or services from us, we ask you for certain financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date) in order to process your order.  While we do not store your credit card information, our payment processors may.  If they do store your information, we do not have direct access to the stored information.  Rather, we only have the ability to submit charges if you purchase additional goods or services from us in the future.

**Physical address:** We may request your physical mailing and/or residential address.  This information is usually only requested when you place an order.  If you are placing an order, we use this address information to process your order (such as to verify financial information) and to create a complete purchase record for your records and for ours.  While we do not currently send postal mail except in extraordinary circumstances, we reserve the right to use your address in the future to send you occasional notifications related to our offerings and/or your account.

**Name and email address:** We may request your name and electronic mailing address in order to provide you with digital materials and communications and to create an account record for you.  This information may be collected when you purchase or download a product or request information or services from us. 

If you are contacting us with a question via our contact form, your email address will only be used to complete the request at hand.  We may create an account based on your name and address to allow tracking of your request, but your name and email address will not be used for other purposes. 

If you provide us with your email address in the context of filling out a lead form, requesting more information about a product or service, entering a contest, making a purchase or downloading a product, your email address will be used to complete the request and you may also be added to our electronic mailing list.  Subscribers to our email list receive the following types of electronic mailings:

  * Account notifications and updates (not regularly sent)
  * Occasional notifications related to products and product updates (usually a few per year)
  * Educational updates (usually one to two per month)
  * Occasional greetings and holiday messages (at most a few per year)

This list of message types is accurate at the time of the publication of this policy, but may not always reflect the latest mailings we send.  Rest assured, though, we hate spam and will never spam you.

You may unsubscribe from our email list or update your preferences at any time at http://www.dwuser.com/unsubscribe/ .  You can unsubscribe from all types of mailings or only certain types of mailings.

We do not share name and email address information with third parties except under the strict circumstances below.  We never sell or rent your information.

**Phone number:** We may request your phone number and/or Skype ID when you are making a purchase, downloading a product, creating an account or requesting information.  We usually only use this information as an alternative contact method to provide important account or purchase updates if other electronic channels (such as email) fail.  At the current time, we do not contact account holders via telephone except in extraordinary circumstances.  However, we reserve the right to use this information in the future to occasionally contact you regarding your account and our products and/or services.

**Survey and other demographic information:** We may ask you to provide information about your preferences, habits and other non-sensitive demographic information (such as age, location etc) in order to provide more tailored and useful services, information and educational content.  We only ask for this kind of information if it directly relates to our products and offerings; we don't think it's cool to be snoops.

**User-generated content and public activities:** We offer you the opportunity to engage in public activities on the Website, such as participation in public discussion and support forums, social sharing, and commenting.  Any information you disclose in your public activities, along with your name, screen name or ID, profile picture and any other public profile data, is posted publicly and may be used by us for commercial or promotional uses.  We will usually ask your permission before using your publicly-posted data for commercial or promotional uses, but this is not guaranteed in all cases.  Please be aware that any personal information you share publicly may be accessed by other visitors and could be misused.  We are not responsible for events arising from the distribution of any information you choose to publicly post or share through the Website.

**Third-party personal information:** We may occasionally collect information from you about other people.  For example, if you order a gift we may collect information about the recipient so we can properly deliver it.  In cases where we collect information from you about another person, we use that information only for the primary purpose at hand: for example, sending a gift.

#### Information we collect passively from you

**Browser-based analytical data:** As you navigate the Website, we may track generic information that your browser provides about your system configuration – such as your language, browser type and version, operating system type and version and screen resolution.  This industry-standard information is used to enhance our products and services and is not shared with third parties in a personally-identifiable form.

**Server-based analytical data:** As you navigate the Website, we may track information such as your IP (internet protocol) address and any referrer site from which you may have arrived.  Your IP address may be used to determine geographic location.  This industry-standard information is used to enhance our products and services and is not shared with third parties in a personally-identifiable form.

**Behavior-based analytical data:** As you navigate the Website and/or use our applications, we may note specific actions you take as you interact with the interfaces.  We may combine this information with log data and chronological information to improve our understanding of how these interfaces are being used.  This information is used to enhance our products and services and is not shared with third parties in personally-identifiable form.

### How We Protect Your Personal Information (Sharing and Disclosure)

We're serious about privacy and simply do not rent or sell your personal information.

We disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of our employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that:

  * (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide services available on the Website (for example, to fulfill an order or send a mailing in our name), and
  * (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. 

Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the Website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. 

Again, we will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.  Other than to our employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, we disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when we believe in good faith that, due to an extraordinary circumstance, disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property, rights or safety of our company or its employees or contractors, third parties or the public at large.

### Options Related to Your Information

**Financial information:** If you are no longer interested in purchasing goods and/or services from us and have no outstanding contracts open with us, you may request that any credit card information stored by our payment processor be removed.  We will then attempt to remove our ability to process charges on your card(s).  To request this change, please use the contact directions below and request that your financial information be removed; include the following information:

  * Your full name
  * The card type
  * The last 4 digits of the card (not the full number)
  * The expiration date of the card
  * Your billing address

**Physical address:** We never want to send you any material in which you are uninterested.  If you ever receive postal mail from us that you would prefer not to receive, please use the contact directions below and request that you no longer receive notifications via postal mail; include the following information:

  * Your full name
  * Your mailing address
  * Details on the specific mailing you received, so that we may verify this as a mailing that originated from us

**Email address:** As mentioned above, you can manage your email list subscription preferences at http://www.dwuser.com/unsubscribe/ .  You may fully unsubscribe from all non-critical mailings at that URL.  (Critical mailings are one-time updates sent in situations where we believe a failure to receive the message could cause you significant harm – for example, notifications of security vulnerabilities.)

**Phone number:** As mentioned above, we currently only use phone number information in extraordinary circumstances.  If you would like to be sure that you never receive any other type of phone communication from us in the future, you may remove your phone number from your account at http://www.dwuser.com/myaccount/#account-details .

**Long-term analytical data:** If you do not wish for long-term analytical data to be gathered as you browse our site, we recommend that you clear your browser's cookies after each browsing session. Please note that this may reduce the overall functionality of our site; for example, you may be forced to log in again or re-enter information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns.  We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of the Website and their Website access preferences.  Cookies allow us to provide functionality such as logging in to your account and adding items to your shopping basket.

If you do not wish to have cookies placed on your computer, you should set your browser to refuse cookies before using the Website.  Keep in mind that this may break core functionality on the Website and will harm your visitor experience.

### Business Transfers

If our company, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party.  You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of our company may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

If we choose to display advertising on our site in the future (we do not display ads at the time of writing), these ads may be delivered through third-party advertising partners.  These partners may set cookies in order to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement and to compile information about you or others who use your computer.  This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.  This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies only by our company and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

### Social Network Integration

On selected pages of the Website, we provide opportunities to share content or communicate through social networks, such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest and Google+.  These social networks may set cookies in order to recognize your computer and account and provide functionality.  This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies only by our company and does not cover the use of cookies by any social networks.

### Other Sites / Links

The Website may link to or contain links to other third party websites that we do not control or maintain, such as in connection with purchasing products referenced on the Website and banner advertisements.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by any third party website.  We encourage you to note when you leave the Website and to read the privacy statements of all third party websites before submitting any personally identifiable information.

### Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information.  In the unfortunate event that your "personally identifiable information" (as the term or similar terms are defined by any applicable law requiring notice upon a security breach) is compromised, we may notify you by e-mail (at our sole and absolute discretion) to the last e-mail address you have provided us in the most expedient time reasonable under the circumstances; provided, however, delays in notification may occur while we take necessary measures to determine the scope of the breach and restore reasonable integrity to the system as well as for the legitimate needs of law enforcement if notification would impede a criminal investigation.  From time to time we evaluate new technology for protecting information, and when appropriate, we upgrade our information security systems. 

### Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important.  For that reason, we never collect or maintain information on the Website from those we actually know are under 13 years of age, and no part of the Website is structured to attract anyone under 13 years of age.  If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and believe he or she has disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us as provided below.  A parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 may review and request deletion of such child's personally identifiable information as well as prohibit the use thereof.

### How to Contact Us and Opt-Out Information

You may contact us as provided below if: (a) you have questions or comments about our Privacy Policy; (b) wish to make corrections to any personally identifiable information you have provided; (c) want to opt-out from receiving future commercial correspondence, including emails, from us or our affiliated companies; or (d) wish to withdraw your consent to sharing your personally identifiable information with others.  If you wish to unsubscribe from our email list, you may also do so directly at http://www.dwuser.com/unsubscribe/ .

Contact us via electronic mail through the contact form available on the bottom of most pages on our site (including the home-page: http://www.dwuser.com/ ).  You may also contact us via United States Postal Mail at the following address:

Magnetic Marketing Corp.  
P.O. Box 50596  
Indianapolis, IN 46250

We will respond to your request and, if applicable and appropriate, make the requested change in our active databases as soon as reasonably practicable.  Please note that we may not be able to fulfill certain requests while allowing you access to certain benefits and features of the Website.
